Guide to the Lewis Zurlo Associates Architecture & Interior Design Collection MS 028
Western Connecticut State University Archives and Special Collections
- Series 5: Photographs & Slides, 46736
  - Photographs (professionally mounted/frameless) 30x40, 47076
    - 1993 The (Union Savings Bank) Galleria, Main Street, On site (architectural) photography, Mark Elliot, 47079 (Item Map folder *, Folder *)
    - 1994 Liberty Terrace (affordable) Condominiums, Liberty Street. On site (architectural) photography, Mark Elliot., 47078 (Item Map folder *, Folder *)
    - 1995 Savings Bank of Danbury Addition. On site (architectural) photography, Mark Eliot., 47077 (Item Map folder *, Folder *)
  - Slides, 46944
    - Adams Residence, 12/85, 1985; 47075 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Adult Probation Center, 6/89 - 8/89, 1989; 47074 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Appel Residence (See Bucholtz), undated; 47073 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Arnold House-Wooster School & Zotos Model, 8/81 - 9/81, 47072 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Audubon Court, 2/90 - 5/90 (see Halpin Court), 1990; 47071 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Barlas Residence, 8/73-10/74, 1974; 47070 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Barlas Add/Ren, Lake Waubeeka, 8/73 - 5/75 (73-03), 1975; 47069 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Barlas Addition/Renovation II, 10/74 - 5/75 (73-03), 1975; 47068 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Barry Law Offices, 9/79 - 5/80, 1980; 47067 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Baruch Residence, 10/71 - 12/73, 1973; 47066 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Berger Residence, 7/73 - 10/79, 1979; 47065 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Berger Interior, 6/75 - 8/75 (75-13), 1975; 47064 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Bicentennial Houses, 5/75 - 3/76, 1976; 47063 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Bigelow Apartments, 4/86 - 9/86, 1986; 47062 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Bishop Curtis Homes, undated; 47061 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Boston/Newport, 6/82 - 7/82, 1982; 47060 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Brushy Ridge, 11/87, 1987; 47059 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Bucholtz/Hoffstatter/Appel, 5/82 - 6/82, 1982; 47058 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Buildings (Misc.), undated; 47057 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Burnett Restaurant, Study Shots for, 10/83, 1983; 47056 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Buscemi Renovation, 4/74 (74-01), 1974; 47055 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Butts Addition, 10/73 - 10/74, 1974; 47054 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Butts Porch, 7/74 - 10/74, 1974; 47053 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Camm Residence, 7/78, 1978; 47052 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Chaykin Residence, 2/75-2/77, 1977; 47051 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - Churches, undated; 47050 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - First Congregational Church Chapel, New Milford, undated; 47049 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - New Hope Baptist Church, undated; 47048 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - United Methodist Church, New Milford, undated; 47047 (Box Slide box 1, Folder *)
    - (Great) Danbury State Fair Auction, 4/82, 1982; 47046 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Danbury Main Street Building Renovations, undated; 47045 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Danbury Buildings, 9/80 - 5/82, 1982; 47044 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Ives Street Firehouse & Omaha Beef Building, 5/80, 1980; 47043 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Downtown Parcel A&B Study/Sipperly Wells, undated; 47042 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Wooster Cistern, 10/80 - 12/81, 1981; 47041 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Danbury Preservation, 9/77 - 5/82, 1982; 47040 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Danbury Preservation Trust Awards, 1989; 47039 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - DeLucia Apartments, 11/89 - 7/90, 1990; 47038 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - DeVoe Insurance/European Furniture, 3/81 - 6/84, 1984; 47037 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - DeVoe (Rear) Addition, 6/89 - 1/90, 1990; 47036 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - DeVoe Office, New Milford, 5/87 - 3/90, 1990; 47035 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Downtown Improvement Plan, undated; 47034 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Emilia Apartments, 12/81, 1981; 47033 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Ericson House, 6/87 - 3/90, 1990; 47032 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Finklestein Addition, 10/75 - 12/78 (77-18), 1978; 47031 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - First Congregational Church, 8/68 - 8/75, 1975; 47030 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Flayderman Residence, 10/72 - 5/74, 1974; 47029 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Garafallo Office Addition, 12/84 - 2/86, 1986; 47028 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - The Godfrey Apartments (Nolan), 7/80 - 6/82, 1982; 47027 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Goo's Lumber, 11/74 - 12/74, 1974; 47026 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Graham House, 9/69 - 4/70, 1970; 47025 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Gruzdzinskas/Levine, 2/78 - 9/78, 1978; 47024 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Halpin Court, 4/89 (See also: Audubon Court), 1989; 47023 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Hatter's Yard, 11/89 - 9/90, 1990; 47022 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Hechter Addition, Lake Waubeeka, 1983-1984; 47021 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Heritage Village, 10/69, 1969; 47020 (Box Slide box 2, Folder *)
    - Hoffstatter, 5/78 - 9/79 (See Bucholtz), 1979; 47019 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Horton Residence (Eliot Noyes Office # 2-3). 1972, 47018 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Hubbard's Cubbard, 12/79 - 5/80 (78-12), 1980; 47017 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Hull Building (DaSilva), 9/77 - 7/79, 1979; 47016 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Hull Building & Signs, 4/80 - 8/82 (80-32), 1982; 47015 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Hull Building Addition, 5/84 - 12/84, 1984; 47014 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - IBM: 7 Penn Center 5th Floor, 8/82, 1982; 47013 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - IBM: 1700 Market, 17th Floor, 9/81, 1981; 47012 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - IBM: 1818 Market, 14th Floor, 4/81 (80-07), 1981; 47011 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - IBM: Merritt 7, 3rd floor, undated; 47010 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - IBM: One Hamden Center, undated; 47009 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - IBM: Hartford, 10th Floor, undated; 47008 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - IBM Pavilion, San Antonio (See Johnson Residence), 1969; 47007 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Ives House, 6/89 - 5/91, 1991; 47006 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Jaber Renovation/Pinney Payne Law Offices, 6/80, 1980; 47005 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Jennings, 6/86 - 12/86, 1986; 47004 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Johnson Residence (Eliot Noyes Office #1), 1970; 47003 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Kalliurousis Residence, 4/91, 1991; 47002 (Box Slide box 3, Folder *)
    - Ladd Restaurant, 5/76 (See: Mall), 1976; 47001 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Lagratta Apartments, 1/82 - 8/82, 1982; 47000 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Lake Waubeeka Beach, 2/67 - 6/75 (75-07), 1975; 46999 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Leed's Design, 11/87 - 2/88, 1988; 46998 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Leili Fire Rebuild, 5/87 - 11/88, 1988; 46997 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Leili Alleyway, 11/88, 1988; 46996 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Leonard Residence, 10/75, 1975; 46995 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Levitt Landscaping, 3/76 (75-18), 1976; 46994 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Levy Addition, 9/74 - 9/77 (73-05), 1977; 46993 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Lewin Residence, 7/80, 1980; 46992 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - 221 Main Street, 2/86 - 10/87, 1987; 46991 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Main Moon, 7/90, 1990; 46990 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Mall, 6/86, 1986; 46989 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Mall Stores (NY Snack Exchange & Roo Roo, Roo), 4/89, 1989; 46988 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Mobil Station Prototypes (See Johnson Residence), 1967; 46987 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Murphy Residence, 1/76 - 5/76, 1976; 46986 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Music Guild Renovations, 6/84, 1984; 46985 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Misc. Buildings, 9/77 - 7/90, 1990; 46984 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - National Ceramic Products, Brookfield, 2/78 - 9/79 (78-02), 1979; 46983 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - New Hope Baptist Church Exterior, 10/75 - 12/78, 1978; 46982 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - New Hope Baptist Church Exterior/Interior, 10/77 - 7/78, 1978; 46981 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Nolan Enterprises Offices, 11/85 - 2/88, 1988; 46980 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Nolan East Liberty Street, 3/78 - 10/79, 1979; 46979 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Nolan Enterprise (221 Main Street), 2/86 - 5/86, 1986; 46978 (Box Slide box 4, Folder *)
    - Northside Animal Hospital, 6/87 - 5/89, 1989; 46977 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Norwalk/New Canaan Shops, 7/79 - 12/83, 1983; 46976 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Noyes, Eliot Office (See: Horton Residence & Johnson Residence), undated; 46975 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Old Library Interior, 11/85 - 4/88, 1988; 46974 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Old Library Addition & Windows, 5/87 - 11/87, 1987; 46973 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Omaha Beef (See Ives Street Firehouse), undated; 46972 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Phelps Memorial Hospital, 9/90 (See VFW), 1990; 46971 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Phineas Park Apartments (Nolan), 7/83 - 7/90 (82-41), 1990; 46970 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Pinney Payne Law Offices (See Jaber), undated; 46969 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Plumtree Plaza, 6/90 - 7/90, 1990; 46968 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Pride Cleaners (Nolan), 323 Main Street, 10/78 - 12/81, 1981; 46967 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Radial Bearings, 6/91, 1991; 46966 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Ranger Residence, 9/83 - 4/85, 1985; 46965 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Rider I, 3/77 - 8/78 (76-05), 1978; 46964 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Rider II, 3/77 - 11/78 (76-05), 1978; 46963 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Rizzo Building, 4/86 - 6/86, 1986; 46962 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Roman Residence, 9/80 - 12/80, 1980; 46961 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Russo Building I, undated; 46960 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Rynkyewitz Renovation (73-06), 1973; 46959 (Box Slide box 5, Folder *)
    - Sandpit Condos, 7/87, 1987; 46958 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - Sipperly Wells (See Danbury Downtown Parcel A & B), undated; 46957 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - Terrace Place (# 6 & 8), 11/87, 1987; 46956 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - Towey Additions, 4/77 - 12/78, 1978; 46955 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - United Methodist Church, 7/76 - 4/80 (76-07), 1980; 46954 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - United Nations Pavilion, World's Fair, Montreal, 1968; 46953 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - Venture 8, 6/73 - 2/75, 1975; 46952 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - VFW Bethel 7/89 - 1/90, 1990; 46951 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - Victorian Houses, 11/79 - 6/84, 1984; 46950 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - The Vincent/New England Uniform, 10/81 - 3/87, 1987; 46949 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - Viola Addition, 6/73 - 8/75 (73-01), 1975; 46948 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - Young's Hotel, New Milford, 11/87, 1987; 46947 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - Zotos Apartments, 7/79 - 5/83, 1983; 46946 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
    - Zotos Model (See Arnold House-Wooster School), undated; 46945 (Box Slide box 6, Folder *)
- Series 6: Zip Disks/CD-RW Disks/Floppy Disks, 46730
  - 1992-1996 Projects: 88 3½ x 3½ disks, undated; 46735 (Box Disk box, Folder *)
  - 1996-2001 Projects: 67 3½ x 3½ disks, undated; 46734 (Box Disk box, Folder *)
  - 1997-2001 Projects: 13 zip disks, undated; 46733 (Box Disk box, Folder *)
  - 2002-2004 Projects:, undated; 46732 (Box Disk box, Folder *)
  - 2002-2004 Projects:, undated; 46731 (Box Disk box, Folder *)
- Series 7: Historic Preservation, 46699
  - Buckhurst Fish Hutton Katz, Inc. Downtown Retail Market, Danbury, CT, April 1988, 46729 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Buckhurst Fish Hutton Katz, Inc. Downtown Danbury Today: Market Conditions and Physical Analysis, May 1988, 46728 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - A Revitalization Plan for Downtown Danbury, July 1988, 46727 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Danbury Bicentennial Home Tour, 1976; 46726 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Danbury Bicentennial Home Tour, 1976; 46725 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
    Seven 10x14 original home sketches for booklet
  - Danbury Bicentennial Home Tour, 1976; 46724 (Item *, Folder *)
    Row 5/bay 3/shelf 5, 10x17 free standing "Rousseau" mounted photo/booklet
  - Business Digest, "Danbury Downtown Facelift", 1984; 46723 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Danbury Miscellaneous, undated; 46722 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Danbury Newspaper Articles, 1976-1999; 46721 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Danbury Newspaper Articles (Historic Building Photos), undated; 46720 (Box 18, Folder 4-5)
  - Danbury Preservation Trust, 1979-1996; 46719 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Danbury Preservation Trust: Historic Preservation Handbook; A Guide to Preservation in Danbury, undated; 46718 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Danbury Preservation Trust: Historic Preservation News, November 1992, undated; 46717 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Danbury Preservation Trust: Mayor's Conference on Historic Preservation, 1980; 46716 (Box OS 1, Folder *)
  - Danbury Preservation Trust: Renews, 1979-1990; 46715 (Box 18, Folder 8-9)
  - Danbury Railway Museum, 1995-1996; 46714 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Danbury Scott-Fanton Museum and Historical Society, 1992-1996; 46713 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Danbury Tricentennial Committee, 1984-1985; 46712 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Ives Street Revitalization Area, v. 1 and v. 2, prepared by the City of Danbury, n.d. (ca 1990), 46711 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Magazine Articles (Miscellaneous), undated; 46710 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - New Milford House Tour, 1957; 46709 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - News-Times Sunday Magazine Sections, 1984-1995; 46708 (Box OS 2, Folder *)
  - Pamphlets (Connecticut), undated; 46707 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Pamphlets (Miscellaneous), undated; 46706 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Restoration Details: Connecticut Historical Commission Guidelines for Application and Selection, Fiscal Year 1987, 1983-1991; 46705 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Restoration Details: Design Guidelines (3), undated; 46704 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Restoration Details: National Main Street Center Handbook, undated; 46703 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Restoration Details: National Trust for Historic Preservation, Main Stree t, 1983; 46702 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Restoration Details: U. S. Department of Interior, Preservation Briefs, 1978-1991; 46701 (Box 18, Folder 21-22)
  - Restoration Details: U. S. Department of Interior, Standards for Rehabilitation and Guidelines for Rehabilitating Historic Buildings (Rev. 1983), 46700 (Box 18, Folder 23)
- Series 8: Personal, 46637
  - Awards (framed), 46690
    - 1990 Danbury Preservation Trust Sunderland Award for Historic Preservation (includes annual dinner booklet), 46698 (Box 29)
    - 1990 State of Connecticut for Historic Preservation, 1994 Pillars of the Industry Award "Best Townhouse", 1990-1994; 46697 (Box 27)
    - American Arbitration Award for serving as arbitrator, undated; 46696 (Box 22)
    - 1952-1953 Music Education League, Third Honors, 4hands, piano, 46695 (Box 22)
    - 1994 City of Danbury for Excellence in Design for 3 projects: The Galleria, Liberty Terrace, 258-268 Main Street Facades, 46694 (Box 22)
    - 1981-1982 Who's Who in the East, 18th Edition, 46692 (Box 22)
    - Lincoln Center Repertory Theater, Seating and Storage & Life Plan (36"x35"), July 5, 1961. Message: "Wish you were here Lew…..", 46691 (Box OS 6, Folder Blueprint:)
  - Licenses (framed), 46682
    - 1958 Pratt Institute, Bachelor of Architecture degree 1965 State of Connecticut Architectural License, 46689 (Box 23, Folder *)
    - 1981 Commonwealth of Pennsylvania License, 46688 (Box 23, Folder *)
    - 1982 Commonwealth of Massachusetts License, 46687 (Box 23, Folder *)
    - 1976 The American Institute of Architects Certificate of Membership, 46686 (Box 23, Folder *)
    - 1979 National Council of Architectural Registration Boards, 46685 (Box 23, Folder *)
    - Member of the American Arbitration Association, undated; 46684 (Box 23, Folder *)
    - Member of the Connecticut Society of Architects, undated; 46683 (Box 23, Folder *)
  - Mounted on Matt Boards (various sizes), 46677
    - 1958 College Thesis (photocopies), 46681 (Box OS 3, Folder 1)
    - 1965 Projects w/John Graham Office, NYC, 46680 (Box OS 3, Folder 1)
    - 1968 First Zurlo Office/Residence, 46679 (Box OS 3, Folder 2)
    - Lincoln Center Theater w/Eero Saarinen (photocopy on foam core), 1962; 46678 (Item 1, Folder *)
  - School Work/Slides/Photographs/Negatives, 46655
    - School Work 50s (Rendering), 1950s; 46676 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - School Work (Jersey Meadows) Negatives, undated; 46675 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - School Work (2-ring 11x15) Original drawings w/text., undated; 46674 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - School Work (3-ring 11½x11½), undated; 46673 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Pratt Institute, 1953-1958; 46672 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Eero Saarinen Office Years, 1959-1963; 46671 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Saarinen/Swanson Reunion Proceedings, 2001; 46670 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Eliot Noyes Associates Years, 1966-1972; 46669 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - New Canaan Historical Society's Modern House Tour, 2001; 46668 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Slide Show (4 sheets) and one sheet miscellaneous, undated; 46667 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Photographs (publicity), undated; 46666 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Negatives (publicity), undated; 46665 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Caricature Negatives, undated; 46664 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - CBS Eye on NY Interview (Jersey Meadows) 2/23/1958., 46663 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - CT-TV Community Forum (Danbury) Interview, 2003; 46662 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Zurlo Table Design Model Prototype, ca 1965, 46661 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Zurlo Lake Residence/Office, 1967; 46660 (Box 30, Folder 10-12)
    - Zurlo 363 Main Street/Office Apartment, 5/77 - 9/78, 1977-1988; 46659 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Zurlo Farview Residence, 1980-1985; 46658 (Box 30, Folder 14-16)
    - Zurlo Farview Interiors, 3/82 - 5/90, 1982-1990; 46657 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Zurlo Residence Addition, 4/88 - 2/90, 1988-1990; 46656 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Miscellaneous, 46638
    - Biographies (original), undated; 46654 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Row 6/bay5/1shelf, Caricature "Zurlo & Kistler" 24½ x 12½ color, undated; 46653 (Box 30, Folder *)
    - Clippings, 1969-2000; 46652 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence (misc.) and clippings, 1964-1989; 46651 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Steve Griss Photos, undated; 46650 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Job List Master, undated; 46649 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Vitae (ca 1980), 46648 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Two seasonal greeting cards (sketches of churches on Mykonos), 1967-1969; 46647 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous (folder), undated; 46646 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - 1985 IBM Letter of Appreciation, 46645 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - 1991 George Davon (fax), 46644 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - 1994 Certificate of Recognition and Excellence in Design Awards, City Center Danbury Recognition Breakfast (invitation), 46643 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - 1997 New Faces and Changing Places (Zurlo Associates relocation to 225 Main Street), 46642 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Future Inserts: 16 color photocopies + 16 written 12 half photocopies + half written, undated; 46641 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Wood & Metal First Sign: Lewis F. Zurlo AIA Architect, undated; 46640 (Box 26, Folder *)
    - DVD Interview -, 2005; 46639 (Box 26, Folder *)
      Meg Moughan, then WCSU Archivist and Special Collections Librarian, interviewed Lewis Zurlo in his home on Friday, November 4, 2005. The meeting was not structured as a formal interview. Moughan and Zurlo viewed it as an opportunity to walk through his home office and studio while having a discussion regarding some of his professional architectural projects undertaken in Danbury, Connecticut and surrounding towns.
    - Interview of Zurlo by Meg Moughan, 2005; 58641
- Series 9: Miscellaneous, 46608
  - Brochures:, 46631
    - Elliot Noyes & Associates, undated; 46636 (Box 25, Item 1)
    - Zurlo+Kistler, Architects, undated; 46635 (Box 25, Item 2)
    - Lewis Zurlo Associates, undated; 46634 (Box 25, Item 3)
    - The Sullivan Architectural Group, undated; 46633 (Box 25, Item 4)
    - K-Man Glass & Insulation (Galleria), undated; 46632 (Box 25, Item 5)
  - Consultants, 46625
    - Collective Design Associates, P.E., undated; 46630 (Box 25, Item 6)
    - GeoDesign, Inc. Geotechnical Engineer, undated; 46629 (Box 25, Item 7)
    - Tom Torrenti, P.C., undated; 46628 (Box 25, Item 8)
    - Errichetti Debacle, 1984-1990; 46627 (Box 18, Folder 50-59)
    - Margot Wormser, CSA / AIA Affordable Housing Program Awards Submittal, 1990; 46626 (Box 24, Folder *)
  - Publications:, 46609
    - 1963 Look Magazine, p.49 (Ericson House), 46624 (Box 25, Item 9)
    - 1983 Money Savings Home Plans, p.62, 46623 (Box 25, Item 10)
    - 1990 Business Digest, p.30, 46622 (Box 25, Item 11)
    - 1993 Connecticut Builder, p.14, 46621 (Box 25, Item 12)
    - 1993 Union Savings Annual Report, 46620 (Box 25, Item 13)
    - 1994 Business Digest, p.4, 46619 (Box 25, Item 14)
    - 1994 Multi-Housing News, p.53, 46618 (Box 25, Item 15)
    - 1994 Pillars of the Industry (Liberty Terrace), 46617 (Box 25, Item 16)
    - 1995 Business Digest (Galleria on cover), 46616 (Box 25, Item 17)
    - 1999 Commemorative History of the Savings Bank of Danbury, p. 1, 4, 64, 67, 46615 (Box 25, Item 18)
    - 2002 The Prime Timers First Annual Dinner Dance to Benefit the New Danbury Senior Center "Elmwood Hall" booklet, 46614 (Box 25, Item 19)
    - 2005 The Benchmark, Caldwell & Walsh, 1981-1982; 46613 (Box 25, Item 20)
    - 2005 Inside Business, p. 5-6 and cover, 46612 (Box 25, Item 21)
    - 2005 News-Times Business, "The Architectural Shape of, 46611 (Box 25, Item 22)
    - 1981-1982 Who's Who in the East, p.869, 46610 (Box 26, Item *)
- Project Photographs, 46737
  Note: (bids & cost estimates may also be included) *Filed Separately photographs/negatives are located in two-drawer metal file. Negatives are 35 mm unless otherwise noted. Main Street Façade blue prints included.
  - Alex's Foreign Auto Parts (93-16), undated; 46943 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    13 4x6 color and negatives
  - Alligator Alley (93-11), undated; 46942 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    3 4x6 color
  - Barlas Addition, undated; 46941 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 1)
    4 5x7 color
  - Barns, undated; 46940 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 2)
    17 4x6 color
  - Barns - Negatives, undated; 46939 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 1)
  - Barry Law Offices (79-18), undated; 46938 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 3)
    One 5x7 color
    6 8½ x 11 color photocopies
  - Barry Law Offices (79-18), undated; 46937 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 1)
    5 4x5 color negatives
  - Baruch Addition/Renovation (71-03), undated; 46936 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 4)
  - Berger Renovation (73-02), undated; 46935 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 5)
    11 3½ x 5 b/w
  - Berger Interior (75-13), undated; 46934 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    47 4x6 color and negatives
  - Bernadino's Furniture, 97-, undated; 46933 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    5 4x6 color
  - Bigelow Apartments (89-21), undated; 46932 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 6)
    11 3½ x 5 color
    3 8x10 color
    One 4x5 negative mounted on 8x10 black board
    3 8½ x 11 color photocopies
  - Bigelow Apartments (89-21), undated; 46931 (Box Photo_box 5, Folder 1)
    One 4x5 negative
  - Bisbano Addition (20-40), undated; 46930 (Box Photo drawer, Folder *)
    12 4x6 color
  - Bishop Curtis Homes, undated; 46929 (Box Photo_box 1, Folder 7-11)
    108 4x6 color
    2 8x10 color